Shubham Singh

Graphic Designer | UI/UX Designer | Front-End Developer

PROFILE

Name

Shubham Singh

Location

Noida, India

Phone Number

+91-7785037144

Email

shubhamsingh1604@gmail.com

SOCIAL

Facebook

facebook.com/shubhmisaki

Twitter

twitter.com/shubhmisaki

Behance

behance.net/shubhmisaki

Dribbble

dribbble.com/shubhmisaki

Github

github.com/shubhmisaki

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

A dedicated and enthusiastic person in the field of graphic design along with experience in UI/UX, prototyping & front-end development.

I thrive to be a professional UI/UX Designer solving complex problems into easy, eye-catching & pixel perfect interfaces.

EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present

Nibble Computer Society

Graphic Designer | UI Designer | Front-End

As a designer of the team, I have the responsibility of creating various designs in form of posters, banners, online posts etc. I also created various user interface designs & did a bunch of front-end web projects.

2017 - 2018

TED[×] JSSATE

Creative Head (Previously Designer)

As a Designer of the team, I had the responsibility of creating various designs for the branding of the event in year 2017 including online posts, ticket designs, flexes, print designs etc. As a Creative Head in year 2018, I had the responsibility of coming up with ideas to brand the event via various designs like IDs, certificate, banners, posts, stickers, passes etc.. along with a

June - Sep 2018

Visit Internet Services

Design Intern

As a Designe Intern, I had the responsibility of creating various designs as per the need of the company which included branding of an event, magazines, icons, infographics, mail designs, UI elements, flexes, brochures etc. Also I created various mailers using HTML.

EDUCATION

2016 - Present

JSS Academy of Technical Education, Noida

B.Tech in Information Technology - 72% Aggregate

(Undergraduate 3rd Year Student)

2012-2015

Lucknow Public School, Lucknow - CBSE Board

- Senior Secondary Board Examination 74%
- High School Board Examination 9.8 CGPA

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe XD Adobe Premiere Pro Balsamiq Wireframing

Prototyping Sketching HTML CSS **Javascript**